<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="FAQs">
        <item>"Click the Eye Icon at the top right of the Home page to Hide or view your Balance."</item>
        <item>"1. Once you click on TeasyPay Mobile App, Input your wallet ID (Wallet number).\n2. Input your PIN and you will be logged into your Home Screen immediately "</item>
        <item>"From the Home at the top left of the Home page to see your Profile Dialog."</item>
        <item>"1) From the Home Click the Profile Icon at the top left of the Home page. \n 2) Select Transaction History to view all transactions."</item>
        <item>"1) From the Home Click the Profile Icon at the top left of the Home page.\n 2) Select Fund Wallet then Any of the Options an follow instruction."</item>
        <item>"1) Click on the  Bell Icon at the top right of the Home page to view all Transfers, \nAirtime Purchase, Bill payment etc."</item>
        <item>"1) Click the Profile Icon on the top left of the home page Select change Pin\n2) Input current pin\n3) Input new pin and confirm it then Click on change Pin."</item>
        <item>"1) Click the Profile Icon on the top left of the home page.\n2) Select and click Register Customer.\n3) Fill all requirements on the Create Account menu and click create my Account."</item>
        <item>"1) Click on Top-up on the Home page\n2)Select buy for self for your wallet number or select for others.\n3)Select Airtime / Data and Input Amount, click on Buy and confirm details\n4)then click on confirm."</item>
        <item>"1) Click on AEDC from the Home page\n2)Select Self to receive the Token or Others if it is a customer\n3) Input Meter Number\n3)Input Amount and click continue to confirm details\n4)Click confirm, input your Wallet pin before final sending."</item>
        <item>"1) Click on DSTV/GOTV on the Home page or Click on Pay Bill on the Home page and select any of the Biller\n2) Input Smartcard Number\nSelect biller type then confirm details\n3) Input your wallet Pin and\nClick on Confirm"</item>
        <item>"1) Click on Swift4G on the home page.\n2) Input modem number from the pop-up menu\n3) Click on swift service and input amount then press OK.\n4) Click on confirm after Validation."</item>
        <item>"1) Click on Transfer or Quick transfer on the Home page\n2) Click on Wallet to Bank\n3) Input Account number, Select Bank and wait for it to Validate account\n4) Input Amount, then input Narration and click on Verify\n5) Confirm details then click on transfer"</item>
        <item>"1) Click on Transfer Cash on the Home page\n2) Select MMO and click on it\n3) Input MMO/Wallet number\n4) Select the MMO and wait for it to Validate number\n5) Input amount and Narration then click on Verify\n6) Click on Confirm/Transfer"</item>
        <item>"1) Click on Transfer Cash on the Home page\n2) Select and click on Wallet to Wallet\n3) Input receiver’s wallet number\n4) Input amount then click on Transfer\n6) Click on Confirm after validation"</item>
        <item>"1) Click on FRSC on the Home page or Pay Bill and select make payment\n2) Input Application ID then click on continue\n3) Confirm details the send"</item>
        <item>"1) Click on NIS on the Home page or Pay Bill and select make payment\n2)Input Application ID then click on continue\n3) Confirm details then send"</item>
        <item>"Your money is safe since every transaction requires your secret PIN before completion except you shared your pin with someone else.\nNOTE: If your mobile phone is lost or stolen, contact us and we will freeze or suspend your mobile wallet account for your protection."</item>
        <item>"1) Deposit N25, 000 into our pool account (5,000 is POS fee while 20,000 is cautionary fee which will be refunded once the POS is returned in good condition)\n2) Provide evidence of payment.\n4)Await SMS alert once your POS is set up.\n5) Sales office will contact agent for training and collection of POS."</item>
        <item>"USING PAX POS\n     Power the pos by long press on the red button\n     On the screen, choose card payment (1)\npurchase (1) and Choose account type Savings (2), current (3) and Credit (4\n     input amount and press enter\n     Insert or swipe Card\n     Give the customer to input his Pin\n     Enter and wait for approval that comes out with customer copy\n     Enter again for Merchant copy\nREPRINT\n     Press MENU on the POS screen\n     Select 1 on the POS screen to reprint\n     Select 1(last transaction)/ 2(by RRN)/3 (All transactions) on the POS screen\n     Enter on the green button to reprint\nPRINTING END OF DAY\n     Press MENU on the POS screen\n     Select 3 on the POS screen\n     Select 1(for today), 2 (by date and input the Date), 3(All transaction)\nSHUTTING THE POS DOWN\n     Shut the pos by long press on the red button\nUSING PAX POS\n     Power the pos by long press on the red button\n     On the screen, choose card payment (1)\n     purchase (1) and Choose account type Savings (2), current (3) and Credit (4\n     input amount and press enter \n     Insert or swipe Card\n     Give the customer to input his Pin\n     Enter and wait for approval that comes out with customer copy\n     Enter again for Merchant copy\nREPRINT\n     Press MENU on the POS screen\n     Select 1 on the POS screen to reprint\n     Select 1(last transaction)/ 2(by RRN)/3 (All transactions) on the POS screen\n     Enter on the green button to reprint.\nPRINTING END OF DAY\n     Press MENU on the POS screen\n     Select 3 on the POS screen\n     Select 1(for today), 2 (by date and input the Date), 3(All transaction)\nSHUTTING THE POS DOWN\n     Shut the pos by long press on the red button "</item>
        <item>"NOTE\n# All POS merchant copy must be save in case of charge back.\n# If transaction is not approved and the customer is debited, please don’t give cash to the customer.\n# All charge back must be treated before 24hrs.\n# Once a printout showed roll back and the customer is debited, please don’t give cash to the customer.\n# Kindly request for customer valid ID for transactions above N150,000\n# For more clarification on complicated transaction, kindly contact agency manager/customer care.\n# You can only access your App on one mobile phone\n# Remember to keep your PIN personal/Safe\nRemember to change your pin once in every three or four months for security reasons\n# View all your pos transactions on the App (Transaction History).\n# Good customer relationship grows your business\n# Separation your personal funds from customer’s funds\n# KYC Know Your Customers"</item>
        <item>"We charge 0.5% from 5₦ - 20,000₦\nWe charge 100₦ flat rate from 20,001 - 355,000"</item>
        <item>"NIS PAYMENT AMOUNT\n\t15,300\n\t17,500\n\t25,300\n\t35,300 e.t.c\nFRSC PAYMENT AMOUNT\n(3 Years)\n\t10,350\n(5 Years)\n\t15,450\nTRANSFERS/DEPOSIT TARIFF.\nTransfer to all Banks   ------- N 15 flat ‘’subject to change’’\nWallet to wallet ------ N 5 flat.\nBILL PAYMENT\nCable TV   ------------- #100 sharing commission 60% -40%\nAirtime Top-up---------- 2% of amount recharged.\nJamb------------------------ #4,700 sharing commission #150\nAEDC------------------Free"</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>